Inventory of the Austin-Twyman Papers, 1765-1939
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Letters, 1765-1939. (Folder 1-159)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1769-1930, n.d. (Folder 150-159)
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1840-1849., 13 items. (Folder 154)
      Letters written by or addressed to James Brown, E. W. Cabell, Jno. Crews, Mr. and Mrs. crews (invitation), B. M. DeWitt, Julia DeWitt, P. A. Forbes, Richard H. Gambria (Western State Lunatic Asylum), Elizabeth Glover, Charles Perrow, Margret S. Phillips, W. H. Plunkett, Webb, Brown & Co., [?] and a letter concerning Frederick C. Horsley's application for a position at the University of Virginia.
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1850-1859., 31 items. (Folder 155)
      Letters written by or addressed to John M. Atkinson, Robert Atkinson, Sarah Austin, Anika Blew (black and perhaps slaves), Dr. James Bolton, [?] Breckinridge, F. M. Cabell, John B. Childers, Bennitt DeWitt, Samuel H. Dunn, Susie Ford, W. Franklin, James M. Fulks (hiring slaves), Sarah J. Garland, Joseph Grow, Jno. F. Hix, W. Hix, Joseph Kyle, Marcus T. C. Loving, Samuel McCorkle, W. A. Miller, [?] Moseley, R. D. Palmer, Peter S. Parker, J. W. Randolph, James H. Rodes, V. W. Southall, Jno. R. Thompson, Charles C. Tucker (land warrant claims), Iverson L. Twyman (concerning eye injury of Iverson L. Twyman, Jr.), George C. Walton, Jno. Walton, Seth Woodruff (selling of slave girls) & McCorkle, Simpson & Jones.
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1860-1869., 28 items. (Folder 156)
      Letters written by or addressed to Ben (slave working on Richmond defenses, 14 August 1864), Ada Bocock, [?] Brownes, Eliza H. Carrington, R. A. Coghill, N. F. Ellis, Richard Ellis, James H. Fitzgerald, P. A. Forbes (concerning escape of Bennett Dodge from Central Lunatic Asylum, Staunton, Va.), H. M. Garland, Jr., William A. Glasgow, J. H. Howell, R. R. Irving, Jeter & Dickinson, Kensey Johns, Harry O. Locher, Samuel McCorkle, A. D. Martin, Doctor John Peter Mettauer, B. G. Morris, Charles Y., Morris (concerning turning in names of all slaves aged between eighteen and fifty-five: 9 February 1864), William F. Oliver (commanding Davidson's Battery and concerning service record of Jessie A. Peters), Camm Pattison, Peyton, Cary & Co., Samuel Read, Jno. J. Riggins, Robert Shaw, Francis T. Stribling (superintendent of Central Lunatic Asylum), J. L. Thornton, Dr. [?] Walton (concerning Robert A. Gilliam, Co. F, 18th Virginia Regiment), James A. Wright.
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1870-1879., 22 items. (Folder 157)
      Letters written by or addressed to Grace R. Bagby, Joseph Brown, Jno. J. Echol, A. Eubank (describing a shooting outside saloon in San Antonio, Tx.), R. H. Gilliam, S. O. Larche, Bennie Lynn, Albert McDaniel, W. D. Moore, W. P. Moseley, Eva S. Newton, William Merry Perkins, Mary Philpott, Willie B. Philpott, Frank G. Ruffin (concerning Grange), James R. Thompson, William E. Walkup (concerning person who needs assistance from county), Samuel Lother Wynn, Jeter & Dickinson, Richmond, Virginia.
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1880-1930., 16 items. (Folder 158)
      Letters written by or addressed to Mrs. J. Curry Abbitt (transfer of church membership for Thomas J. Davidson), Alice Bagby, A. J. Clore, Jr., Rosa V. Cole, J. W. Falson, George Hylton, Mrs. Paul A. Klayder (concerning Twyman genealogy), Nelia Miller (concerning Twyman genealogy), J. H. Montgomery, D. A. Richardson (for Armenian Relief Committee of Chicago), W. J. Sadler, Idah Meacham Stobridge, Robert M. Tarleton, S. Reed Vaughn, New Canton Motor Company.
    - Miscellaneous Letters, n.d. (Folder 159)
      Many are incomplete and fragmentary. Genealogical material. Includes letters written by or addressed to George E. Booker, Charles L. Cocke, Bennitt M. DeWitt, Minnie Ellis, John Abner Eubank, Charles R. Fontaine, Thomas W. Garnett, E. G. Grasty, V. Hill, W. Hubard, David Kyle, Carol Martin, [?] Perkins, James Rowland, William Sands, W. Thompson, Nettie Walker (enclosing photograph of "The Willows"), Samuel D. Williams, E. A. Wright, James A. Wright, cloth fragment. Genealogical material, ca. 1850.
- Minutes of a meeting of citizens of Buckingham County, November 1827. (Folder 160)
  Minutes of a meeting of citizens of Buckingham County, "friendly to the Election of General Andrew Jackson as...[the] next President."
  Series 2: James River and Kanawha Company Papers
- James River and Kanawha Company Papers, 1847-1879. (Folder 161-164)
  - James River and Kanawha Canal Papers, 1847-1857., 12 items. (Folder 161)
    Includes letters written by Flippen & Montgomery, [Lynchburg ? Virginia], W. Gill, James M. Harris, John H. Hill, J. M. Spiller, James C. Turner, Iverson Lewis Twyman.
    See also J. M. Spiller letters and Twyman and Spiller manuscript volumes.
  - James River and Kanawha Company, 1858-1859., 15 items. (Folder 162)
    Papers relating to the canal. Letters written toJames M. Spiller by Thomas Harding Ellis and E. Lorraine. Minutes of the President and Directors of the James River and Kanawha Company. James M. Harris to Iverson L. Twyman.
  - James River and Kanawha Company, 1860-1879., 25 items. (Folder 163)
    Papers relating to the canal. Includes letters written by or addressed to Frances A. Austin, Grace B. Austin, J. G. S. Boyd, E. L. Chinn, Thomas H. DeWitt, Thomas Harding Ellis, J. M. Harris, William P. Munford, Jno. B. Robertson, Francis H. Smith (of Virginia Military Institute), James M. Spiller; and receipts.
  - James River and Kanawha Company. 1855-1856, n.d., 2 items. (Folder 164)
    Papers relating to the canal. Time book for Gwynn Dam & Lock. Drawing - section of finder. Gwynn Dam, n.d.
- Slavery items, n.d., 2 items. (Folder 165)
  Draft of note about whipping a slave. Form of bill of sale of slave. (Other slavery items among dated papers).
- Peter Francisco. 1802-1829, n.d., 24 items. (Folder 166)
  Legal papers involving him. Concerns money owed by Francisco.
  Series 3: Accounts and Legal Papers
- Accounts and Legal Papers, 1765-1919, n.d. (Folder 167-404)
  - Austin Family, 1796-1872, n.d. (Folder 167-231)
    - Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1796-1872, n.d. (Folder 167-221)
      - Accounts, legal papers and correspondence, Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1796-1779., 17 items. (Folder 167)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1800., 24 items. (Folder 168)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1801., 41 items. (Folder 169)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1802., 50 items. (Folder 170)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1803., 63 items. (Folder 171)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1804., 41 items. (Folder 172)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1805., 55 items. (Folder 173)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1806., 82 items. (Folder 174-175)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1807., 88 items. (Folder 176-177)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1808., 65 items. (Folder 178-179)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1809., 53 items. (Folder 180-181)
        Folder 180 includes a copy of John Randolph agreement with James Hall, dated 27 April 1809.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1810., 73 items. (Folder 182-183)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1811., 84 items. (Folder 184-186)
        Folder 184 includes 2 items involving Thomas Jefferson, Jr.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1812., 44 items. (Folder 187)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1813., 57 items. (Folder 188-189)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1814., 50 items. (Folder 190-191)
        Folder 190 includes 2 items signed by Edmund Henry.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1815., 54 items. (Folder 192-193)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1816., 60 items. (Folder 194-195)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1817., 29 items. (Folder 196)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1818., 24 items. (Folder 197)
        Includes item signed by Edmund Henry about a legal matter.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1819., 34 items. (Folder 198)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1820., 43 items. (Folder 199-200)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1821., 40 items. (Folder 201)
        Includes copy of legal paper involving Edmund Henry.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1822., 49 items. (Folder 202)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1823., 45 items. (Folder 203)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1824., 31 items. (Folder 204)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1825., 32 items. (Folder 205)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1826., 33 items. (Folder 206)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1827., 35 items. (Folder 207)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1828., 41 items. (Folder 208)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1829., 23 items. (Folder 209)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1830., 26 items. (Folder 210)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1831., 31 items. (Folder 211)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1832., 31 items. (Folder 212)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1833., 27 items. (Folder 213)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1834., 27 items. (Folder 214)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1835., 20 items. (Folder 215)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1836., 20 items. (Folder 216)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1837-1839., 15 items. (Folder 217)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1840-1842., 21 items. (Folder 218)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1843-1849., 38 items. (Folder 219)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), 1850-1872., 26 items. (Folder 220)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Archibald Austin (1772-1837), n.d., 74 items. (Folder 221)
    - Archibald Austin (1815-1886), 1841-1857., 12 items. (Folder 222)
      Accounts and Legal Papers.
    - B. Austin and Bernard Austin, 1810-1858., 13 items. (Folder 223)
    - Frances Austin, 1848-1863., 47 items. (Folder 224)
    - George B. Austin, 1842-1855., 108 items. (Folder 225)
    - Grace R. and Grace B. Austin, 1842-1871., 91 items. (Folder 226)
    - James Austin, 1811-1862., 12 items. (Folder 227)
    - John Austin, 1801-1857., 101 items. (Folder 228)
      Accounts and Legal Papers. Apparently more than one person by this name.
    - Martha Austin 1839-1840., 2 items. (Folder 229)
      Accounts and Legal Papers. See also Martha E. Twyman.
    - Thomas Austin, 1806-1869., 126 items. (Folder 230)
    - Unidentified Austins or more than one name per paper, 1804-1869, n.d., 44 items. (Folder 231)
  - Twyman Family, 1820-1939, n.d. (Folder 232-274)
    - Leverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1820-1839., 84 items. (Folder 232-233)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1820-1829., 13 items. (Folder 232)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1830-1839., 71 items. (Folder 233)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1840-1869. (Folder 234-257)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1840-1841., 40 items. (Folder 234)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1842-1843., 66 items. (Folder 235)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1844., 38 items. (Folder 236)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1845-1846., 62 items. (Folder 237)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1847., 49 items. (Folder 238)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1848., 73 items. (Folder 239)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1849., 65 items. (Folder 240)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1850., 38 items. (Folder 241)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1851, 40 items. (Folder 242)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1852., 64 items. (Folder 243)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1853., 57 items. (Folder 244)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1854., 73 items. (Folder 245)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1855., 94 items. (Folder 246)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1856., 117 items. (Folder 247)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1857., 69 items. (Folder 248)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1858., 97 items. (Folder 249)
        Includes statement of 27 February 1858 of sale of a Negro man for $1075.00 by D. M. Pulliam & Co., Richmond, Va. A/c Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1859., 78 items. (Folder 250)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1860., 93 items. (Folder 251)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1861., 84 items. (Folder 252)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1862., 89 items. (Folder 253)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1863., 51 items. (Folder 254)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1864., 37 items. (Folder 255)
        Includes receipt, 6 August 1864, for Negro slave to work on fortifications.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1865., 20 items. (Folder 256)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Dr. and Mrs. Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864), 1866-1867., 36 items. (Folder 257)
    - Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, 1868-1910, n.d., 302 items. (Folder 258-262)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, 1868-1869., 48 items. (Folder 258)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, 1870-1871., 73 items. (Folder 259)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, 1872-1879., 35 items. (Folder 260)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, 1880-1910., 20 items. (Folder 261)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Martha E. Twyman, Iverson L. Twyman (1810-1864) Estate, n.d., 86 items. (Folder 262)
    - Iverson L. Twyman, Jr. (1849-1921), 1870-1910., 55 items. (Folder 263-264)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Iverson L. Twyman, Jr. (1849-1921), 1870-1879., 38 items. (Folder 263)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Iverson L. Twyman, Jr. (1849-1921), 1880-1910., 17 items. (Folder 264)
    - Augusta Twyman, Fanny Twyman, George Twyman, James Twyman, Jean Twyman, 1733-1939., 17 items. (Folder 265)
      Accounts and Legal Papers. Copy of a George Twyman will of 1733, and last advices of another George Twyman, 1803. Other Twyman items 1873-1939.
    - John A. Twyman, 1870-1939, n.d., 223 items. (Folder 266-272)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1870-1879., 14 items. (Folder 266)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1880-1889., 33 items. (Folder 267)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1890-1899., 24 items. (Folder 268)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1900-1909., 49 items. (Folder 269)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1910-1919., 11 items. (Folder 270)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1920-1929., 75 items. (Folder 271)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of John A. Twyman, 1930-1939, n.d., 17 items. (Folder 272)
    - Samuel R. Twyman, 1880-1925., 44 items. (Folder 273)
    - Various Twymans: Absalom Twyman, Dr. John L. Twyman, Dr. Lewis J. Twyman, 1849-1852., 4 items. (Folder 264)
  - Accounts and Legal Papers with two or more last names, 1830-1909, n.d. (Folder 275-283)
    - Twyman - Austin, 1830-1879., 112 items. (Folder 275)
      Accounts and Legal Papers. Papers involving both names.
    - Twyman - Horsley, 1843-1859, n.d., 250 items. (Folder 276-282)
      Papers involving both names.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1834-1842., 30 items. (Folder 276)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1843., 55 items. (Folder 277)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1844-1845., 51 items. (Folder 278)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1846-1847., 21 items. (Folder 279)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1848-1849., 27 items. (Folder 280)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1850-1851., 42 items. (Folder 281)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of Twyman - Horsley, 1852-1859, n.d., 24 items. (Folder 282)
    - Twyman - Spiller, 1847-1909, n.d., 56 items. (Folder 283)
  - Horsley Family, 1809-1850, n.d. (Folder 284-288)
    - John Horsley, Robert Horsley, 1809-1829., 31 items. (Folder 284)
    - Robert Horsley, 1830-1839., 142 items. (Folder 285)
    - Robert, William, Ann and Rebecca Horsley, 1840-1849., 117 items. (Folder 286)
    - Robert Horsley, Wm. Horsley, n.d., 24 items. (Folder 287)
    - Horsley and other families, 1811-1850., 7 items. (Folder 288)
      Accounts and Legal Papers. Horsely - Austin, 1811. Horsley -Spiller, 1818-1850. Papers involving both names.
  - Spiller Family, 1807-1909, n.d. (Folder 289-325)
    - George Spiller, James M. Spiller, 1807-1835., 195 items. (Folder 289-292)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of George Spiller, James M. Spiller, 1807-1830., 55 items. (Folder 289)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of George Spiller, James M. Spiller, 1831-1832., 22 items. (Folder 290)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of George Spiller, James M. Spiller, 1833., 58 items. (Folder 291)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of George Spiller, James M. Spiller, 1834-1835., 60 items. (Folder 292)
    - James M. Spiller, 1836-1839., 64 items. (Folder 293)
    - George A. Spiller, Sara Ann Spiller and James M. Spiller, 1840-1849., 58 items. (Folder 294)
    - James M. Spiller, Preston F. Spiller and others, 1850-1851., 19 items. (Folder 295)
    - James M. and other Spillers, 1852-1909, n.d. (Folder 296-325)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1852., 22 items. (Folder 296)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1853., 49 items. (Folder 297)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1854., 44 items. (Folder 298)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1855., 59 items. (Folder 299)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1856., 118 items. (Folder 300)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1857., 87 items. (Folder 301)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1858., 70 items. (Folder 302)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1859., 70 items. (Folder 303)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1860., 99 items. (Folder 304)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1861., 103 items. (Folder 305)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1862., 40 items. (Folder 306)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1863., 29 items. (Folder 307)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1863-1866., 21 items. (Folder 308)
        Includes bill of James M. Spiller of 1863-1864 to Confederate States of America for hay, corn, etc. Also pardon from Andrew Johnson to James M. Spiller for "taking part in the late rebellion."
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1867-1868., 195 items. (Folder 309)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1869., 106 items. (Folder 310)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1870., 81 items. (Folder 311)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1871., 161 items. (Folder 312)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1872., 164 items. (Folder 313)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1873., 103 items. (Folder 314)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1874., 28 items. (Folder 315)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1875., 26 items. (Folder 316)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1876., 30 items. (Folder 317)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1877., 46 items. (Folder 318)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1878., 32 items. (Folder 319)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1879., 16 items. (Folder 320)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1880-1882., 35 items. (Folder 321)
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1883-1885., 57 items. (Folder 322)
        Includes dentist's bill of period 1873-1883 finally settled in 1887.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1886-1889., 63 items. (Folder 323)
        Includes copies of will of 1889 of J. M. Spiller.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, 1890-1909., 73 items. (Folder 324)
        The majority of the material concerns Miss Mary Spiller.
      - Accounts and Legal Papers of James M. and other Spillers, n.d., 41 items. (Folder 325)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1774-1928, n.d. (Folder 326-371)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1774-1799., 65 items. (Folder 326)
      Includes part of deed dated 1 May 1784 signed by Benjamin Harrison, Governor.
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1800., 40 items. (Folder 327)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1801., 27 items. (Folder 328)
      Includes papers on the estate of William Adams.
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1802., 20 items. (Folder 329)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1803., 30 items. (Folder 330)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1804., 32 items. (Folder 331)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1805., 33 items. (Folder 332)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1806., 32 items. (Folder 333)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1807., 33 items. (Folder 334)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1808., 49 items. (Folder 335)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1809., 25 items. (Folder 336)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Legal Papers, 1810., 45 items. (Folder 337)